

CONTACT

- +31653446300
- ✓ jurekledzinski@yahoo.pl
- Engelenkampstraat 70 6131JJ Sittard
- frontend-craftportfolio.netlify.app

EDUCATION

2010 - 2014

The West Pomeranian
University of Technology in
Szczecin

 Engineer of Environmental Protection

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS/Styled components
- Javascript/Typescript
- React
- Next.js
- Node/Express
- MongoDB
- Git

OTHER SKILLS

- Driving license
- Driving Heftruck/EPT/LPT

LANGUAGES

- English (Intermediate)
- Polish

CERTIFICATES

- Web developer from beginner - HTML, CSS
- Advanced frontend HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery
- Programming in javascript
- · React.js from beginning
- Node Express.js, MongdoDb

JERZY LEDZIŃSKI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Junior Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience specializing in React.js typescript. Passionate about web development and dedicated to enhancing skills and expanding knowledge in building modern, user-friendly interfaces. Actively seeking new challenges to support continued professional growth in the frontend field.

LINKS

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jurek-ledzinski

Github: https://github.com/jurekledzinski

WORK EXPERIENCE

Enventico B.V.

Junior frontend developer

September 2024 -October 2022

- I participated in building a very large project in React typescript for the Belgian company "Nedschroef Machinery", which is still developing.
- Working with reusable components: I developed and optimized React components, which contributed to simplifying the code, making it easier to scale and maintain.
- API integration: I implemented API calls, retrieved data and managed its state using Context API, which allowed for dynamic updating of content on the page.
- API integration was based on using react useQuery and mutations.
- Performance optimization: I analyzed and improved the application's performance, using techniques such as lazy loading or component rendering optimization.
- Application testing: I wrote end-to-end tests using tools such as React cypress.
- Team collaboration: I worked with a team of developers, using Git for version control and tools such as Jira for task management.
- I used css, styled components, designed system.
- · The work was also based on data modeling.

Ceva Logistic Born

May 2020 -December 2018

Marshalling goods and loading

- Work with dlx warehouse management of system.
- · Analyzing data.
- · Control flow of the orders.
- · Shipping orders in the system.
- Administration
- · Contact with expedition and customer service.
- · Loading/unloading trucks.
- · Loading goods according to the scheme.
- Checking received goods according to documentation.
- · Send orders according to the plan of the despatch.
- Organization of warehouse space, placing orders, scanning.
- Driving heftruck, EPT, LPT.